Viewers, begin to ask for a greater understanding
of God's heart because Jesus is Lord over your life .
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Greater understanding of God's heart because Jesus is Lord over your life - prayer.
Greater understanding, Jesus is Lord over your life.
I release you, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever bondage you find yourself in -
your marriage, your finances - be released, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
You can give your best with the grace of God, if you are not in a cage.
Whatever cage you find yourself in - generational cage, knowingly or unknowingly,
I release you, in the name of Jesus!
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
I can sense God's release.
Be released!
Right now, those of us who are under the influence of my voice -
I release you, in the name of Jesus!
Viewers all over the world, according to His Word, "Come unto Me all ye that are sick and poor";
according to His Word, I deliver you, in the name of Jesus!
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
According to His Word, be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Receive, in the name of Jesus!
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Be healed!
Begin to give thanks to God for giving you faith to believe.
Give thanks to God right now.
I can sense God's healing right now.
I can sense God's deliverance touching your blood, skin, kidneys, liver, bones, blood, fluids!
Right now, give thanks to God for giving you faith to believe.